## **Jadson Santos**

Front-End Developer passionate about crafting exceptional, fast, and responsive web experiences

Brio de Janeiro, RJ, Brazil

jadsondossantos5@gmail.com
+5521999577807



## **About**

With 4 years of experience as a Front-End Developer, my expertise in ReactJS and NextJS enables me to create responsive and optimized web pages for multiple devices. I stand out by significantly enhancing performance through refactoring strategies and implementing script automations via Google Tag Manager. I am committed to code reviews, ensuring excellence and adherence to best practices.

# **Work Experience**

#### Red Ventures Brasil Remote

2021 - 2023

Web Programmer

Implemented new features, worked on improving the apps performance, developed and maintained the front-end of web applications. Technologies: React, JavaScript, GatsbyJS

#### Commerce Growth Rio de Janeiro

2019 - 2021

Front-End Development Trainee → Jr Front-End Developer

Developed and maintained high-performance e-commerce sites. Documented and implemented tracking tags (Google Analytics, Google Ads, Facebook Pixel) via GTM. Technologies: VTEX CMS, JavaScript, Sass, Pugjs, Gulpjs

#### Nasajon Rio de Janeiro

2017 - 2018

Front-End Development Intern

Collaborated with WordPress, implementing custom features and themes

### **Education**

#### State University of Rio de Janeiro

2011 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

#### **Skills**

JavaScript TypeScript React/Next.js HTML5 CSS3 Sass VTEX CMS

# **Projects**

#### **Thalita Torres**

Thalita Torres's portfolio, showcasing her skills in design, usability, and user experience

Side Project JavaScript

Next.js CSS3 Sass Modules

**EmailJS** 

## **Shopping Cart**

Lists, searches, and manages products from the Mercado Livre API, featuring functionalities to add and remove items

Side Project JavaScript

Reactjs API

### **Primeflix**

Project that lists movies from The Movie DB API, allowing users to add and remove favorites

Side Project Sass JavaScript

Reactjs API